My name is Anmol Duggal and I'm from
Rohtak, Haryana.
I'm a 27-year-old software engineer
working in an IT company in Delhi NCR.
When I shifted to a big city, I saw a
lot of accidents happen at very young
age. People like me are passing away,
which put a financial burden to their
families. So, I decided to buy a term
plan to protect my family from the
financial burden. [music]
I started searching online for different
term plans and also consulted my friends
regarding the same. So, they suggested
me to invest in the term plan that is
ICICI Prudential iProtect Smart Plus. I
bought this plan from the ICICI
Prudential website and my entire buying
journey was very smooth. When I put all
the details on the website, everything
was so clearly mentioned that I got to
know my premium, my tenure. Besides my
online buying experience, the customer
care support was also very good. I got
all my tests done on time and my policy
was issued very quickly. The best part
about buying the plan from ICICI
Prudential Life is their claim
settlement ratio is very high. Also,
since I'm working in a private sector
where jobs are uncertain, there is a
feature in the policy is we [music] can
hold the premium for completely 1 year.
That is very good in my case. Also,
there is a benefit in this plan if my
tenure is over and nothing happened to
me, I will get my premium back. Since I
have bought this plan, now I am fully
secured, my family is also secured. I
don't have any stress in my life that if
something really bad happened to me, my
family will suffer
financially.
>> [music]